It's really tight! My sh** barely fit!
Hi and welcome to a new video here on my channel!
It's going to be super exciting today because we have so many different fabrics.
We have PVC, new premiere on my channel, latex and another PVC dress all from Honor clothing.
So I hope you're going to have fun.
I'm going to tell you a bit more about honor clothing in a sec but first I'm
going to switch into this first PVC dress. First dress it's a simple PVC
dress and I think it makes a great figure and body shape. I can totally
recommend this one if you search for something that's easy to dress, easy to
wear but it looks good because you're into it in like a few seconds and it's comfortable
and yeah I think it's a cool look especially together with some heels and I don't know a bag
or something of course you can hear all these creasing noises typically for pvc I know honor
clothing for quite a while I think the very first latex dress I owned was from honor and it was
really cool and kind of fit me but I sold it eventually so I can't show it to
you here at the moment only pictures but yeah if you're looking for a webshop for
alternative fashion webshop with a lot of variety a lot of products check them
out they have like all the materials latex PVC wet look fall leather real
leather neoprene lace normal fabric so have a look I'll link it down below of course
I said I'm going to show you a lot of fabrics today so PVC was one of them and
the next one is going to be latex it's a latex blouse and color combination red and black with a lot of
snaps that's the word I was looking for and I'm quite curious about the cut I
just washed it it smells good it's also shiny already
welcome back to the latex outfit it's just a simple skirt I had at home but
the blouse from honor in red and black and I think it looks cool it's a bit
like the teacher secretary style I don't know but yeah it has puffy sleeves I like puffy sleeves
white arms so easy to dress that's always a good investment latex that's easy to dress because
then you're really fast and it's better to wear it anyway I quite like the design
and the overall style. I closed almost all the snaps but I think I can open another one.
Yeah, that's a bit more playful so I think I'm going to go with that version. And yeah, otherwise
I like the look. It fits, the arms are really long which is really a good sign. And as I said before
I already own the dress by honor and the latex garment quality is really good
I can totally recommend it if you want to start with latex and look into the topic and try some pieces then
Have a look at their webshop. I've also a video about latex care and
I've been asked a question lately if
If it's too warm in latex and I was like it really depends on the outside temperature
temperature if it's too cold outside and you're freezing it's if it's too warm
you're sweating because latex does not isolate if you want to keep warm then go
with the PVC dress because that's really warm compared to latex but anyway that
was just a bit off topic so completely closed a bit more uptight and I think I
I prefer the open versions. It's not too high and I think it looks still good with my neck that it's not too long but
works perfectly together with this collar here
I'm super happy with the blouse. I think it was a great choice, but I'm really excited about the next garment
Because it's going to be neoprene
Something
It's not similar, but it's also not that kind of different because it's something special so to say.
But well compared with the PVC dress it looks really small.
So let's see if I'm going to fit into this one.
Yay, I managed to squeeze into it and it's like shapewear effect plus 100.
It's not uncomfortable. I mean I can feel that it's a bit tight, but it's okay.
and it looks just really awesome
Don't want to move around too much, no, just kidding
The touch is really soft and yeah
basically what you think of if you think about neoprene
I like the design feature here with the stitching or crosses, whatever
It's purely designed. There's no function behind this. But I think it shakes the design a bit so it's not too plain and not too boring. And I also love the cleavage here. What can I say? I think it's stunning. It looks really great.
This is the first time I'm showing neoprene on my channel. It's also my very very first neoprene item I own.
I quite like it and I know that a lot of shops always call various materials neoprene, but no, this is the real deal.
This is what scuba suits are made of.
I think I'll switch into the last outfit, a PVC dress again, which is a bit wider than this one.
Okay, this is the last dress.
It's PVC again.
There are some differences to the first PVC dress.
The zipper here is in the back and not in the front.
So it is closed completely with a collar and a belt.
And it's also longer.
almost until my knees. So I think it gives you more of a dominant look, I have to say it.
I hope you enjoyed this video and got to know Honor clothing a bit better. If you don't
know them already, check out their homepage. As I said, a lot of materials, a lot of cool
pieces and if you already know them, tell me in the comments if you already own something
from Honor Clothing. By the way I have to say thank you to Honor Clothing for supporting this
video. I hope I'll see you in another video of mine. If you want to support this channel you
can support me on Patreon. I'll link everything down below. Otherwise I hope you're having a nice
day. See you around. Bye!